Mickey Mantle had this much water pressure,he'd have hit 60 before Maris.
Mickey Mantle(美国职棒球员)家的水压要是这么好 他早就能超Maris 60分了
After that,all you can talk about is baseball and plumbing?
在这种时候 你难道还要说些 什么棒球和水管的事吗?
Oh,this game's going extra innings.
哦 这场比赛可是决胜局
- You think you can knock it out of the park? - Oh,I know I can.
- 你觉得你能打出全垒打吗? - 我相信自己没问题的
- Oh,yeah? - Oh,yeah.
- 是吗? - 当然
- You okay? - Yeah,that was weird.I just got a chill.
- 你没事吧? - 有点儿奇怪 我打了个寒颤
Did you get your flu shot?There's a bug going around.
你有打疫苗吗? 最近有流感
I haven't been sick since 1996.
我自打1996年起就没得过病了
Now,come on,I'm up to bat,and you - You feel hot.
- 来 该我拿球棒当击打手了 - 你额头很烫
You look hot.
你更火辣
Well,this game's rained out.I'm taking your temperature.
比赛中止了 让我测测你的体温
Oh,honey.No,please,come on.We can play through this.All right?
哦 亲爱的 别 求你了 咱们打完这局比赛 好吗?
Come on,batter up.
来吧 热身完毕了
Open up.
张嘴
Colony collapse,Neal.
蜂群崩坏综合症 Neal
That's what we're dealing with here.
这是咱现在要处理的大事
Apis mellifera are dying off in terrifying proportions.
西方蜜蜂正以骇人的比例灭亡
Timmy Nolan Park.
公共花园报
People for the awareness of near earth objects,and now the plight of the honeybees.
近地飞行物观测者 现在你又关心起蜜蜂的困境了
Our nation's agriculture depends on these drones.
我国农业发展可是全靠这些小嗡嗡
Without pollination,there's no strawberries,no almonds - No grapes?
- 没有它们授粉 就没有草莓 没有杏仁 - 连葡萄也没有吗?
Is this about wine?
说到头是为了葡萄酒吗?
Maybe.You have room for three hives.
也许吧 你看你家能放下三个蜂巢
That's three more beehives than I want on my terrace.
我可不要我的阳台多出三个蜜蜂窝
I mean,is beekeeping even legal in New York?
我说 在纽约市养蜂恐怕违法吧
Across all five boroughs.I mean,where's the danger?
在五个行政区是违法的 不过 这哪有什么危险性啊
Swarms spring to mind.
我能想到一大堆呢
Although a hive would be a decent hiding spot for contraband.
不过 蜂巢倒是私藏违禁品的好地方
And an excellent business opportunity.
更是优良的商机
Pollen,propolis,and honey have been known for their healing properties since Ancient Greece.
自古希腊以来花粉 蜂胶和蜂蜜的 治疗效用就广为人知
And Cleopatra bathed in milk and honey,and,take it from me,what it did for my undercarriage...
埃及艳后曾在牛奶盒蜂蜜中洗浴 跟你说 我的下身也...
Okay.Start with one hive.
好吧 先来一个蜂巢吧
See you later.
回见
Probably just allergies.All those trees dropping pollen everywhere.
可能只是过敏 现在这些树 正到处撒花粉呢
I do love how leafy this neighborhood is.
这附近的确绿化得很美
What is Neal doing here?
Neal在这干嘛?
Does he have a tracker on you?
莫非他在你身上也装了跟踪器?
Told him I was walking you to work.
我告诉他要送你上班了
- Morning,Peter. - Morning.
- 早安 Peter - 早
- Elizabeth.
-Elizabeth -早安
Want me to carry that for you?
我来帮你拿那个?
- You're casing her art. - What?
- 你在打她的艺术品的主意 - 什么?
You're casing my art?
你在打我艺术品的主意?
Please.You guys qualify for the friends and family plan.
得了吧 你俩电话不都 绑定亲情号码了嘛
I don't know what that means.
这话我怎么听不懂呢
Speaking of families...
说到家庭...
Oh,yeah,that's unbelievable.Figure your kid's dead...
哦对 难以置信 想象一下你的孩子死了...
Then after 15 years,Patrick shows up at the front door.
15年后他又突然出现在家门口
How does a 14-year-old evade an international manhunt?
14岁的孩子是怎么躲过国际搜查的?
When was the last time you saw him?
你最后一次见他是什么时候?
The summer before my junior year.
上中学前那年夏天
Oh,I fell in love with Europe.
哦 我爱上了欧洲
We were going to museums in every city,and it was one of the best tutoring jobs I ever had.
我们去了所有城市里的博物馆 那是我接过的最棒的辅导工作
But then he ran away from boarding school in Switzerland,and I never heard from him again.
不过后来他从瑞士的寄宿学校逃走 我就再也没有他的消息了
Must be nice to have a father who welcomes you home with old masters.
有一个用满屋子大师作品 欢迎你的父亲一定很爽
He wanted a lot of new pieces before the homecoming party.
他想在返家派对之前弄到更多新作品
Oh,well,it will be nice to see him and William,and,wow,Bea was just a baby.
哦天 能见到他和William一定很开心 而且 哇 Bea那时还是个小宝宝
And of course Stanton.
当然还有Stanton
- Who's Stanton? - The butler.
- Stanton是谁? - 管家
He was kind of the glue that kept the family together.
他就像维持家庭关系的黏合剂
Just one butler?Very frugal for gazillionaires.
就一个管家? 真是简朴的亿万富翁
Okay,I'm leaving.Hey,by the way,I'm gonna be putting alarms on the art.
好吧 我要走了 对了 我会在艺术品上安装报警器的
- No. - Just one.
- 不行 - 就一下嘛
What's going on?You sick?
发生什么了? 你生病了?
Come on.The Mortensen Real Estate scandal's not gonna solve itself.
走吧 Mortensen房地产丑闻 可不会自己解决
I wish it would.
真希望它能
Mrs.Burke.Do come in.
Burke夫人 快请进
Stanton,you still can call me Elizabeth.
Stanton 你可以继续叫我Elizabeth
Unfortunately,I cannot.
很不幸 我不能了
Good day.
祝你顺利
Dad,you can't fire him.
爸 你不能开除他
I'm telling you it's a violation of labor rights.
这是对劳动权益的侵犯
Bea,when you have graduated from Harvard Law,we'll continue this conversation.
Bea 你从哈佛商学院毕业后 我们再来谈这个问题
But Stanton didn't do it.
但不是Stanton干的
- Elizabeth. - William.Is this a good time?
- Elizabeth - William 我来的时机不对吗?
Of course.This is my daughter Bea.
没有的事 这是我女儿Bea
I met you when you were a baby.
上次见你时还是个小婴儿
Mm,I've heard the stories.
嗯 我听说过你的故事
And I'm not going to law school.
我没有去法学院的打算
Elizabeth,my apologies.
Elizabeth 真抱歉
Bea spends so much time with her head stuck in novels
Bea花了太多时间在读小说上
that the realities of life are all the harsher.
可现实总是很严峻
Is it true about Stanton?What happened?
Stanton的事是真的吗? 到底发生了什么?
He leaked the truth about my health to the press.
他将关于我健康的真相泄露给了媒体
It was damaging to my business and a personal betrayal.
这不仅损害我的事业 更是对我个人的背叛
I'm really sorry to hear that.How are you?
真遗憾 你还好吗?
Well,blood sugar spikes like the market,ticker's on Mile 24,but screw the doctors.
血糖值像股票市场一样飙高 心脏功能受损 让医生们见鬼去吧
Now that Patrick's home,I feel like I'm 40 again.
Patrick都回家了 我感觉年轻了二十岁
And?How is he?
那么 他状况如何?
Well,he's Patrick.
他还是那样子
As you know,art was the only thing we had in common,
你明白的 艺术是我们唯一的共同语言
and I'm still hoping that's a way we can connect.
我始终希望这也能成为我们沟通的渠道
Liz Mitchell.I'm coming in.
Liz Mitchell 我进来了
Patrick?You're taller.
是Patrick? 你长个儿了
And lost the blue hair.
不再染蓝头发了
I like this better.
现在的样子更好
You are as beautiful as ever.
你还是以前那样漂亮
Yeah,that got us kicked out of the Accademia in Florence.
是的 那不正是咱们 被踢出佛罗伦萨学院的罪魁祸首么
Wow,you still have your scar too.
喔 你的伤疤还在
What was that name of the horse again?
那匹马叫什么名字来着?
- Cheval Chase. - Yes.
- Cheval Chase - 没错
Threw me clear over the fence at Stony Hill.
它把我从Stony Hill的篱笆上扔了出去
Mm,and that was the first time I thought I'd lost you.
嗯 那是我第一次以为我要失去你了
- I'm gonna go check on Bea. - Okay.
- 我去看看Bea - 好的
All right,kid,I've got a lot of questions.
好吧 孩子 我有很多问题想问
After mom died,I begged dad to let me stay in the city with him and Bea.
妈妈死了以后 我求爸爸 让我和他与Bea呆在一个城市
I was so sad about your mom.
你妈妈的事情真令人遗憾
Dad wanted me to go to Le Rosey.But I wasn't ready.
爸爸想让我去萝实学院 可我没有心理准备
- Is that why you ran? - I was tired of living on his terms.
- 所以你跑了? - 我不想再听他指手画脚
You were just a kid.How did you do it?
你当时那么小 到底是怎么做到的?
Saved my allowance.
靠我存下来的零用钱
On a ski day,I snowboarded from Zermatt to Cervinia,
在滑雪日 我从策马特用滑雪板 去了切尔维尼亚
sold my gear,hopped on a train,and never looked back.
卖了我的装备 坐上火车 再没回头
You put your family through hell.
你的家庭可是陷入了水深火热
What made you come back?
你为什么回来了?
Dad.Rumors that he was sick were all over the papers.
因为我爸 报纸上全都是 他病了的传言
I came back for him,not for this life.
我是为了他而回来 不是为了在这里这样生活
He's trying.
他在试着挽回
By buying me art?
就用几件艺术品?
- It's his way of bonding.Let him. - Okay.
- 这是他和你亲近的方式 理解他吧 - 好吧
Well,I remember your tastes.
我还记得你的品味
We have Dutch masters,baroque,abstract expressionists.
我们有荷兰大师 巴洛克风格 和抽象表现主义
That one.The Picasso.
那个 毕加索的那个
The Homme Au Cornet?
吃甜筒的男人?
I put this in as a joke.
我将它看成是个玩笑
Do you remember the Reina Sofia?
你还记得索菲亚博物馆吗?
You called Guernica a bastard child of cubist-surrealist mentovem
你将格尔尼卡叫做 立体超现实主义的水泥砖
and accused Picasso of crimes against beauty.
还指责毕加索破坏了美感
I was a kid.Tastes change.
我那时很小 口味是会变的
- You sure? - Yeah.I love it.
- 你确定? - 是的 我很喜欢
Well,I'll have the gallery send it over.
那我让画廊把它寄过来
Elizabeth.How's Downton Abbey?
Elizabeth 唐顿庄园之行如何?
I know this is gonna sound weird,but I don't think Patrick Wolcott is Patrick Wolcott.
我知道这听起来会很奇怪 不过 我觉得Patrick Wolcott 不是他本人
It's his eyes.They're the right color,but it doesn't feel like him.
眼睛的颜色没错儿 可我总觉得不像他
- You think he's an imposter? - So it's possible.
- 你觉得是个冒名顶替的? - 很有可能
Yeah,missing rich kids are a subset.
对 失踪的富翁之子 是不错的下手对象
You got your Patty Hearsts,your John Paul Gettys,talented Mr.Ripleys.
咱们有不少Patty Hearst(曾被绑架的富家女) John Paul Getty(因对待儿子冷酷无情而与妻子离婚的富翁) 和天才雷普利(著名电影中的罪犯)们
William Wolcott is a perfect mark.
William Wolcott是个很显眼的目标
A very sick,emotionally fragile mark.
病重而感情脆弱的目标
Will you look into it?
你会查查这点吗?
Yeah.I have to run it by Peter,but...
是的 我得通过Peter 可...
- How he's holding up? - I will find out.
- 他还好吗? - 我会去看看的
How are you feeling?
你感觉如何?
Tip-top.Million bucks.
好极了 人生的巅峰
Even if he is a ringer,you're telling me William Wolcott wouldn't know his own son?
就算他是个骗子 William Wolcott 难道认不出自己的儿子吗?
Emotion is a con man's sweet spot.
骗子最喜欢钻感情的空子
And I have good reason to believe that that is not the real Patrick.
而且我有充足理由相信他是假Patrick
- Better be good. - It is.
- 最好是好理由 - 好着呢
- Better be damn good.
- 最好是特别好的理由 - 特别好
Does your wife's intuition count?
你老婆的直觉算不算好?
El called you?
El给你打了电话?
I did say you guys were on the friends and family plan.
我有说过你俩入亲情号码的事吧
Is this some elaborate ruse to avoid the Mortensen case?
该不会是你精心设计的 想要摆脱Mortensen一案的诡计吧?
Okay,that hurts my feelings,because we're looking at potential identity theft,fraud.
好吧 这可伤我的心了 咱们可是在讨论潜在的身份盗窃 诈骗案
A family's fortune is at stake,not to mention the charitable foundation.
一个家庭的幸福危在旦夕 更不用说那些公益基金了
- Based on what? - Pablo Picasso.
- 理由到底是什么? - 帕布罗・毕加索
Kid hated his work,and now he's pushing Elizabeth to buy one.
那孩子讨厌毕加索 可现在 他却要Elizabeth买他的作品
You want me to launch into an investigation based on a Picasso snafu?
你让我因为某人对毕加索的好恶改变 就发动调查?
Peter,this is like you suddenly becoming a Red Sox fan.
Peter 这就像是你一夜之间 成了红袜队的死忠球迷
- I'd have to be... - I'm...you'd have to what?
- 那我得... - 我... 你得怎样?
- I'd have to be a different person. - Thank you.
- 我得先变成另一个人才行 - 多谢
- It's hot in here. - Yeah,you really don't look good.You should go home.
-这里真热 -是啊 你脸色真差 你还是回家吧
I'm not going home.I'm not sick.I've never gone home sick.
我不要回家 我才没生病 我从没请过病假
You're gonna have to give me more than Picasso.
你要给我比一幅画更多的证据
Also suspicious...Mr.Wolcott fired his butler of over 30 years.
还有可疑点... Wolcott先生解雇了 为其工作三十余年的管家
- Good help is hard to find. - Or he was set up.
- 好管家没那么容易找 - 或许他是被陷害的
The smart move is to jettison anyone who intimately knew the real Patrick.
扫除掉了解真正的Patrick的人 才是明智之举
- We'd need a DNA test. - His father hasn't ordered one.
- 我们要做个DNA鉴定 - 他父亲还没有做这个
But Elizabeth could grab a hair when she's over there.
但Elizabeth去的时候可以找点毛发
Okay,I'm not sending my wife in as a secret agent.
我不会让我妻子作为秘密特工过去
- So send me in. - How?
- 那就让我过去 - 怎么做?
The Wolcotts need a new butler.I can buttle.
Wolcotts家族需要人管家 我可以
- Buttle? - Yeah,it's a verb.
- 管家? - 对 那是个动词
Neal Caffrey at your service.
Neal Caffrey为您服务
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-静静的生活
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 安 Zzinc 雅 尘沙 校对: 时差雪 时间轴: 静静的生活
<font color=#238E68>white.collar.Season5Episode5
妙警贼探 第五季 第 5 集
I don't air dirty laundry.
我不对外宣扬丑事
I see that it's cleaned.
我当做没事发生
I did not speak with the press.
我也不接触媒体
Oh,thank you.
谢谢
Yes.Would you like one?
你要来一杯吗?
Excuse me.
抱歉
One pours from the right.
水是从右边倒的
Always from the right.May I?
总是从右边倒的 我来吧
Are you feeling warm,sir?
你觉得热吗 先生?
I am.But I've got my own,thanks.
是的 我自己有手帕 谢谢
Stanton,you're not under investigation,but we do have questions about Patrick.
Stanton 我们不是在调查你 但我们想问你些关于Patrick的事
Do you have any reason to believe this isn't him?
你有无理由相信他不是本人?
He's grown,of course.But the mannerisms...
他长大了 但有些举止...
If it isn't,he's a brilliant study.
若非本人 那肯定下了大功夫去学
If he is a fraud,you could have exposed him.
如果他是个骗子 你或许能揭发他
He might have sabotaged you.
他可能陷害过你
We need physical evidence.A DNA mismatch would prove he isn't a Wolcott.
我们需要物证 如果DNA不匹配 就能证明他不是Wolcott家的
Thanks to Elizabeth's recommendation,William hired me as your replacement.
多亏了Elizabeth的推荐 William雇了我来顶替你的空缺
Excuse me.You?
抱歉 你吗?
Rhett Carlyle,domestic artist.
Rhett Carlyle 管家中的大师
He buttled in a castle in Hampshire.
他在汉普郡的城堡中管家过
- It's a verb. - I am aware.
- 这是个动词 - 我知道
How long did you work in Hampshire?
你在汉普郡工作多久了?
Till he was caught with a princess.
直到他和公爵夫人厮混被发现
Suspected.Never caught.
被怀疑而已 没有被发现
But the evidence was overwhelming.
虽然证据确凿
I didn't steal the silverware.
我又没有偷银器
There is more to private service than consorting with the landed gentry.
私人服务不仅是陪伴有封地的贵族
In addition to scheduling valet and chauffeur duties,
还要安排男仆和车夫的工作
one needs to develop an acute sense of observation.
这需要敏锐的观察力
You wear your Oxfords with a luster,not a shine,lattice-laced.
你穿着有光泽的牛津鞋 而不是耀眼格子边的
Carpal tunnel in your wrist,probably from years of pouring from the right.
手腕上的腕管 可能是因多年从右侧倒水形成
- And,Peter...Peter. - Yes.
- 另外 Peter... Peter - 什么
Muscle fatigue,dry lips,watery eyes,nausea--
肌肉疲劳 嘴唇变干 泪液分泌 有恶心感
I am a brilliant study,and this man has the flu,so you might want to keep your distance.
我领悟能力很强 这个人得了流感 所以你可能想和他保持点距离
My life's work has been protecting that family.I want that to matter.
我一生的工作就是保护这个家庭 我希望这有帮助
Then tell me everything I need to know about taking care of the Wolcotts.
那告诉我一切 照料Wolcotts家需要知道的东西
Carlyle.
Carlyle
Chauncey's ready for his walk.
Chauncey已经准备好出去走走了
Thank you,Miss Bea.
谢谢 Bea小姐
There's a reading of Franny and Zooey at the 92nd Street Y.
在Y街92号有个关于 "Franny和Zooey"的读书会
I managed to secure you two tickets.
我想办法为你弄到了两张票
Mid-century American fiction.My weakness.
中世纪美国小说 我的弱点
Come on,Chauncey.
来吧 Chauncey
- Hey,Bea. - Hey,Patrick.
- 嘿 Bea - 嘿 Patrick
Say hi,Chaunce.
打个招呼吧 Chaunce
How was your ride?
骑车好玩吗?
Every morning there's something else I remember about this city.
每个早上我都能记起 关于这城市的一些事
May I take your helmet,sir?
我来拿您的头盔吧 先生?
No,I am gonna fix the strap.
不用 我要修一下这个皮带
May I take your jacket?
您的外套给我吧?
No,I got it.
不用 我自己能行
You must be thirsty.
您一定口渴了
My father thinks people need servants.I don't.
我父亲认为需要仆人 但我不觉得
- I can take care of myself. - Of course.
- 我能照顾好自己 - 那当然
Mr.Wolcott,the Times,Herald,and Guardian all open to the financial section,
Wolcott先生 泰晤士报 先驱报 卫报都翻到了财经部分
and your Amaranth toast with almond butter's in the dining room.
您的苋菜吐司配杏仁酱已在餐厅
My blood sugar and I thank you,Carlyle.
我和我的血糖都谢谢你了 Carlyle
- Elizabeth,good morning. - Good morning,William.
- Elizabeth 早上好 - 早上好 William
- Carlyle. - Good morning,Mrs.Burke.
- Carlyle - 早上好 Burke太太
Carlyle is wonderful.Where did you get him?
Carlyle非常棒 你从哪找到他的?
Oh,he actually worked for a family that I'm very close to.
其实他以前在我一个密友家工作
The Picasso's coming this morning,and I have a De La Tour to show you.
毕加索的画今早就会送到 我还有幅德-拉-图尔的画给您看
Let's have a look.
我们看看吧
Nice uniform,slick.
制服不错 好打扮
The family hired a team of private investigators...
这家族雇佣了一组和国际刑警合作的
- worked with Interpol... - Hey,Peter,you try acetaminophen?
- 私人侦探... - Peter 你吃扑热息痛了吗?
Ibuprofen?
布洛芬呢?
The daytime stuff,the nighttime stuff?
那些日服夜服的东西呢?
What about the pink stuff?
安非他命呢?
Okay.
好吧
- Peter Burke. - Yeah,stay in there.
- Peter Burke - 好的 待在里面
You're kicking me out?
你要把我踢出小组吗?
- No!No,no,no,just...just taking the appropriate medical precautions. - Okay.
- 不 不 不 你尽快去看医生吧 - 好的
You can see the map,right?Everything's good?
你能看到地图吧? 一切都好吧?
Patrick got out of Germany on a barge.
Patrick搭游艇离开德国的
The family paid a ton in tips.
这家族给了丰厚的小费
Most of them happened right after he ran from school.
多数是在他逃学之后给的
He was first spotted at the train station in-- Dusseldorf.
他第一次被人发现是车站... 在Dusseldorf
Peter,go home.We got this.Okay?
Peter 回家吧 我们能行 好吧?
Caffrey is doing his thing.Go home.
Caffrey在忙他的 回家吧
Oh,I got my tie.
我弄到我的领带了
Nothing.
一无所获
And it's the bottom of the eighth inning...
这是第八局的尾声...
- Neal,hey. - You sound terrible.Where are you?
- Neal 嘿 - 你听上去很糟 你在哪?
I'm working from home.
我在家办公
Mr."No Sick Days"" went home."
"从不请病假"先生回家了
Did you get the evidence?
你找到证据了吗?
It's gonna be harder than we thought.
这会比我们预想的难
I dusted Patrick's glass.He wiped it.
我检测了Patrick的杯子 他清理过
You sure about that?
你确定?
Yeah.Hairbrush is clean.Toothbrush...and razor are sanitized.
是的 梳子很干净 牙刷... 和剃须刀都消毒了
The surfaces are spotless.Either this guy's a total neat freak...
表面一尘不染 这家伙要么是有洁癖
Or he has a reason to be living without leaving a...trace.
要么是他需要不留痕迹地... 活着
Is he this careful all over the house?
他在这家到处都这么谨慎吗?
Yeah,he wouldn't even hand me his bike helmet.
是的 他连单车头盔都不肯给我
He's careful.I think Elizabeth's right.
他很谨慎 我觉得Elizabeth是对的
Yeah.She usually is.
对 她一向如此
- I gotta go. - He onto you?
- 我要先走了 - 他发现你了?
It looks great,you guys.Thank you so much.
看上去很好 谢谢你们
Sorry,Liz.Didn't mean to scare you.
抱歉 Liz 我不是故意吓到你的
It's okay.I was just admiring the Picasso.
没事 我只是在欣赏Picasso的画
Remember those guards who threatened to call The Policia
记得当时我高调地反对立体派时
when my manifesto against cubism got too loud?
那些门卫威胁要找警察吗?
And I used every Spanish word I knew just to charm them.
我用尽我所有西班牙词汇 去转移他们注意力
You promised that we would go to a bullfight if I kept my mouth shut,which was a lie.
你答应我要是我安静就带我看斗牛 结果你骗了我
But we did go to Tapas at Casa del Abuelo,and you let me have a cana,
但我们还是去了Casa del Abuelo吃小吃 你还让我吃了甘蔗
which was sent over by that matador who took a shine to you.
那还是一个喜欢上你的斗牛士送的
- Antonio. - Paco.
- Antonio - Paco
It all came back to me.
我都想起来了
Eventually.
终于想起来了
Sir?
先生?
Miss Bea?
Bea小姐?
Would you mind keeping it down a little bit?I'm working on a genealogy project.
你能说话小声点吗? 我在做一个关于家谱的课题
Apologies.I mistook it for snooping.
抱歉 我误以为你在偷看
Seems we have a pot-kettle situation.
貌似这是五十步笑百步吧
No comment.
不予置评
- Find anything interesting? - Um,travel journal.Fairly informative.
- 有发现什么有意思的吗? - 旅行日记 很多信息
You know,I grew up hearing all about my brother,
我成长的一路都听着我哥哥的故事
and now that he's actually here,he's only told me things I already know.
现在他真的在这 他只和我说些我已知的事情
Maybe you could ask about his travels.
或许你能问问他旅行的事
It doesn't seem like he really wants to talk to me.
他好像不太想和我聊天
I'm sorry,Miss Bea.
抱歉 Bea小姐
And now Stanton's fired,and dad's really sick.
现在Stanton被解雇 爸爸病重
Soon he'll be gone too.
不久就会离世
And then it'll just be me and Patrick.
到时候就只剩我和Patrick了
And you don't want to be left with someone you don't know.
而你不想和你不熟悉的人一起生活
Why are you in here?
你怎么在这里?
I thought you could wear this to dinner tonight,sir.
先生 我觉得您可以穿这个去晚宴
Tell my father no matter how many designer coats he crams in my closet,I'm not wearing one.
告诉我父亲 无论他往我衣柜塞多少名牌服饰 我都不穿
May I ask,how does a teenager evade an international search?
我想问 一个年轻人怎么避过国际搜寻的?
Doctored my dorm mates' passports,
伪造我室友的护照
used 'em to cross borders,and then traded 'em when I needed supplies.
用它们穿过边界 我需要补给时 就把这些卖了
Bartered to conserve cash.Clever.
物物交换 节约现金 真聪明
Colored contacts,a baseball cap.
隐形眼镜 棒球帽
Switched up your accents and avoided Portofino in July?
改变口音 在七月离开菲诺?
Santorini was more my style.
我更喜欢圣托里尼岛
- Is that your journal? - Tales of my travels.
- 那是你的日记吗? - 旅行见闻
Looks like it got wet.
看上去掉进水里过
Dropped it in the Aegean.
掉进爱琴海了
- You're lucky,sir. - Why's that?
- 先生 你真幸运 - 此话怎讲?
After all this,your father will take you back.
经过这么多 你父亲还接纳了你
Why not put on a jacket,make the old man happy?
不如穿上外套 让老人家开心一下?
Carlyle,you are something else.
Carlyle 你真是了不得
Enjoy your dinner.
晚宴愉快
'Cause I got your print.
因为我有你的指纹了
Honey,herbal tea.
亲爱的 草药茶
Okay.And I got ginger.
好的 里面放了姜
And oscillococcinum.
还有欧斯洛可舒能
I don't eat things that I can't say.
我不吃自己不认识的东西
At least tell us how you lifted the cuff link while I eat things I can't say.
在我吃自己不认识的东西时 至少告诉我们你怎么把袖扣偷到手的
PDA.
PDA
Public display of affection?
公共场合亲密行为?
- Elizabeth,can I use your jacket? - Sure.
- Elizabeth 我能借用你的外套吗? - 当然
I'm not sure I like this.
不知道我会不会喜欢这个
Clip this to your left sleeve.
把这个别在你左袖口上
This is not going to work.
这才不会成功呢
Oh,it's gonna work.I'm gonna steal something right off your wrist.
噢 当然会成功 我能直接从你手腕那儿把东西拿走
- Watch. - Oh,I'm watching.
- 看吧 - 我正看着呢
Proximity manipulation.
近距离操作
Diversion technique.
分散注意力技巧
Attention control.
注意力控制
Proximity,diversion,attention.PDA.
缩写就是PDA
It's still there.
可它还在啊
From your other wrist.
注意你另一只手腕
I even told you what I was gonna steal.
我刚才已经告诉你们我要偷什么了 （英语”手表”和”看吧”为同一词）
Wristwatch.You have a gentle touch.
腕表 真是温柔的接触
Oh,oh,that's enough.
噢 噢 真的够了
Hey,Jones.
嘿 Jones
Oh,better.
噢好多了
Got it.Thanks.
知道了 谢谢
Well,do you have a magic trick that can turn bad news into good news?
你有把坏消息变成好消息的魔术吗?
Why,what's up?
怎么 发生了什么?
The prints on the cuff link were perfect,
袖扣上的指纹很完美
except they belong to a person who's never committed a crime.
然而指纹的主人并没有犯罪记录
And it wasn't common to fingerprint kids when Patrick was younger,
那时候Patrick还小 一般不会让孩子登记指纹
so he's not in the database.
所以他不在数据库里
I could send it to Quantico for a mitochondrial DNA test.
我可以把它送到匡提科军事基地 做线粒体DNA测试
That takes too long.I can get some actual DNA,and we can run the test here.
那样太费时间 我能搞到真正的DNA 我们就在本地做测试
Return the cuff link and try my technique..G.A.F.
把袖扣还回去 试试我的手法 GAF
- G.A.F. - Grab a fork.
- G.A.F - 抓回一把叉子
Grab - literally steal the silverware.
抓... 你直接说偷银餐具不就完了
You're a cliche.
你真是掉书袋
Get over it.
习惯就好
He's grumpy when he's sick.Lean back.
他一生病就脾气暴躁 往后躺
- Hey,what's up? - Oh,hey.Yeah.
- 嘿 都发生啥了? - 噢 还成
How's life on Golden Pond?
在金色池塘的生活如何?
And I see you opened the Brunello.
我注意到你打开了一瓶布鲁耐罗
- Oh,yeah,I saved you...Enjoy. - Thanks.
- 哦 没错 我给你留了些 好好享受 - 谢了
- Moz. - Oh,for once I'm not the only one in the room with a buzz.
- Moz     - 噢 这还是头一次 我不是这屋里唯一发出嗡嗡声的
It's loud for one hive.
只有一个蜂巢 怎么声音这么大
I may have acquired three.
我可能弄到了三个的
Skinny Gianetta got nabbed,so his wife put out feelers.
瘦Gianetta被抓走后 他老婆就更小心谨慎了
So in addition to me being undercover as a butler and taking care of Peter,
那么我现在除了要办成管家当卧底 照顾Peter
I'm now the guardian of orphan bees.
还成了蜜蜂孤儿的卫士了?
What ails the Suit?
条子先生得了什么病?
It's that flu that's going around.
就是现在到处传染的流感
That's perfect.
完美至极
It seems fitting that a man of his persuasion should be my Guinea pig.
像他那样信念坚定的人 应该很适合做我的小白鼠
18 amino acids packed into an antimicrobial,flavonoid-filled,
内含18种氨基酸及抗菌类黄酮的蜂蜜补药
honey-based tonic that will rid you of your symptoms and also cure warts,
不但能去除各种临床症状 还能治疗皮肤疣
elevate your mood,and enhance performance.
改善心情 提高性能
Thank me later.Or don't.
你可以之后再感谢我 或者还是算了
- Don't.
- 算了吧 - 算了
I'm supposed to drink this?
我是要把这个喝下去吗?
One now,the second in two hours,and the third within four hours of the first.
现在喝一瓶 两个小时后喝第二瓶 四个小时之后喝第三瓶
Oh,I must be crazy to even consider this.
我肯定是疯了 居然打算喝下这个
- Could you feel any worse? - Probably not.
- 喝下去了情况会更糟么? - 应该不会
I got to get to the Wolcotts.Feel better,Peter.
我得去Wolcotts家了 早日康复 Peter
I'll stay here and observe.
我就留在这儿观察结果
Observe what?What's gonna happen?
观察什么? 会发生什么事?
Well,the first 15 minutes - well,let's see.
呃 头15分钟会... 呃 我们还是等等看吧
Well,it's going to happen.
好的 就这样了
Dad,it's not what I want.
爸 我并不想这样
It's what I want.Consider that.
可是我想这样 考虑一下吧
My attorney is sending it over.
我的代理律师会送过来的
- May I take your cup? - No.
- 需要再加一杯吗? - 不了
No.
噢
So this conversation's over.
这事就这么定了?
In my mind it is.
我认为是这样的
Let's talk about something else.
我们来谈些别的吧
Did you know that Picasso used to burn his own work for warmth?
你知道毕加索当年为了取暖 曾经烧掉了自己的画吗？
That's right.He did.
没错 他真的那么做过
Sir.
先生
Oh,this was a mistake.
噢 弄错了
It was supposed to go to the business manager.
本来应该送到市场经理那儿去的
Here you go.
给你
- Thank you. - Good afternoon.
- 谢谢 - 再见
Time for vial number two.
该喝第二瓶啦
Where'd Mozzie go?
Mozzie去哪儿了?
He needed to check on his queen.
他要去看看皇后的情况
Assuming he meant bee,but with him...
我估计他是指蜜蜂 但他这人...
You never know.
还真不好说
This came for you.
这是寄给你的
I can't open it.It's for William Wolcott.
我不能拆 信封上写的是William Wolcott
But it's addressed to Peter Burke.
但收信人却是Peter Burke
You know,I think your wife had to open it for you because you're extremely sick.
知道吗 我觉得你的老婆不得不替你拆信 因为你病得超严重
Besides,no one will ever know.We can just reseal it.
再说了 没有人会知道的 我们可以把它重新封起来
Neal's a very bad influence on you.
Neal真把你带坏了不少
- Oh,yes. - That was perfect.
- 噢 好了 - 好极了
Neal found out what Patrick's after - a trust fund.
Neal找出Patrick真正想要什么了 一份信托基金
He was supposed to inherit it when he was 21.
他本来应该在21岁时继承的
They're redoing the paperwork today.
他们今天重做了文件材料
- $40 million. - Yeah.
- 四千万美元 - 对
Honey,if he gets that,he's gonna disappear.
亲爱的 如果他拿到这个 马上就会消失
William's heart can't take that.
William的心脏承受不了这种事
I got to let him know what's going on.
我这就把真实情况告诉他
No.Bring William to the FBI.I want to talk to him.
不 把William带到FBI去 我要跟他谈谈
I'm not sure what this Patrick is capable of.He could be dangerous.
我不确定这个Patrick能干出什么事来 他可能很危险
Babe,look,this is a hard conversation to have with a father,
宝贝 要知道 对一个父亲来说 这是很艰难的的谈话
and it needs to come from a friend.Besides,you need to take it easy.
需要由一个朋友来说 另外 你也要放轻松
No,I don't want to take it easy.
不 我才不想放轻松
- I feel better. - Well,that's great.
- 我感觉好多了 - 噢 那太好了
I'll let you know how it goes at the Wolcotts',okay?
我会告诉你Wolcott家的情况的 好吗?
Besides,I want you to lay down.
而且 我希望你能躺下来
William,I'm not trying to upset you.
William 我不是打算让你心烦
Being married to an FBI agent has made you cynical.
嫁给FBI探员后你就变得愤世嫉俗了
It's time for your Insulin,sir.
老爷 您该注射胰岛素了
This has nothing to do with Peter,okay?
这事和Peter无关 好吗?
- I was fooled too. - I'm offended,Elizabeth!
- 我也被愚弄了 - 我现在很生气 Elizabeth!
The whole house can hear you.
整幢房子的人都听到你们在吵了
This is ridiculous.
这太荒谬了
Patrick should have no problem consenting to a blood test.
Patrick应该会答应做个血液测试的
You don't believe me?
你不相信我?
Fine.Draw the blood right now.
好吧 现在就抽血
I don't need this,Patrick.
我不需要你这样做 Patrick
She does.How many others think you're a fool?
但她需要 还有多少人认为你是傻瓜呢?
I won't stick a needle into my own son.
我不会用针刺自己的孩子的
Okay.I'll do it.
好吧 我来
There.Test it.
给你 去做测试吧
The house is equidistant from the avenues,but we don't want him to get that far.
房间和各条道路是等距的 不过我们并不想让他跑那么远
Entry and exit points of the Wolcott residence,upper windows too.
Wolcott家住宅的进口出口 还有楼上的窗户
We're gonna have three agents by the utility van,two more undercover... - Three more.
- 运载车那里会有三名探员 卧底的是另外两名... - 另外三名
Look,Peter,you're a biohazard.
那个 Peter 你就是个有害病毒传播体
I'm on the mend.I swear.And after this...
我发誓我正在好转中 而且喝了这个以后…
- What is it? - I don't know.
- 这是啥? - 我不知道
- Mozzie gave it to me. - Oh,God.
- Mozzie给我的 - 噢 老天啊
It works.I'm in on this bust.My wife is in there.
但是真有效 我要参加这次突袭 我老婆还在里面呢
- When it all goes down,we'll move in for the arrest. - Good boy.
- 等真相大白后 我们就进去逮捕他 - 好孩子
Come on,Chauncey.
来吧 Chauncey
It looks like Mozzie's tincture's working.
貌似Mozzie的药剂起作用了
I'm coming off the DL.
我不用上DL名单了
Baseball.Disabled list.
棒球术语 负伤名单
Did you check out the lab they used to test the blood?
你检查过他们做血液测试的实验室了?
It's reputable.I put an agent there in case Patrick tried anything.
那儿很有名 我安插了一个探员 以防Patrick有什么动作
William had the sample picked up from the house.
William在家里也采了血样
I sealed it and handed it to the technician myself.
我亲自把它封好交给技术员了
So Patrick didn't tamper with it.
这样Patrick就没法做什么手脚了
No,but I'm sure he has something planned when the DNA comes back a mismatch.
是的 不过我很确定 就算DNA不匹配 他也早就想好了计划
I want to know what it is.Audio.
我倒是很想知道他怎么应对 录下来
Check one,two.Check one,two.
测试 听得到吗
I'll keep an eye on Elizabeth.
我会留心着Elizabeth的
Come on,Chaunce.Come on.That's a good boy.
来吧 Chaunce 好孩子 走吧
Everything all right,Miss Bea?
Bea小姐 一切都还好吗?
The blood tests are back.
血液测试结果出来了
What we have here,Carlyle,is a real moment of truth.
Carlyle 现在就是见证真相的时刻了
Everyone,I have news,and you need to hear it.
所有人都听着 我有事情要宣布
You've all been working very hard to prepare for the party on Sunday,
你们全都在辛苦工作 准备周日的派对
but there's been a change of plans.
但现在计划有变
The celebration will now take place tomorrow.
明天的庆祝活动取消
I don't want to wait any longer to welcome home my son.
我一点也不想再等了 我要马上欢迎我的亲儿子
I'm so glad to be back.
能回到家里我简直太高兴了
I shouldn't have put you through this.
我不应该让你经历这些事的
The DNA was a match.
DNA测试的结果匹配
Also I want to thank Elizabeth for all that she's done.
我也要感谢Elizabeth所做的一切
Today is her last day.
今天是她在这儿的最后一天
William,I'm sorry.
William我很抱歉
- You know I was just thinking of you and Bea. - The days I have left with my son are numbered.
- 你知道我这只是为你和Bea在考虑 - 我能留给我儿子的日子已经没几天了
Forcing him to do this,he could have walked out the door,and it would have been your fault.
逼着他做这个 他可能会离开这个家 那样就都是你的错了
I'll send your check.
我会把支票寄给你
What did I do?
我都做了些什么?
Well,I'm fired,and you don't have to be a butler anymore.
我被炒了 你也不用再继续当管家了
I can't just leave.
我不能这么走了
Maybe I'll see how French that maid really is.
也许是我觉得那个女仆有多法式
Liz.I tried to talk to my father,but you know how stubborn he is.
Liz 我试着和爸爸谈了 但你知道他有多顽固
Well,he's upset with me,and I can understand that.
他对我很失望 但我理解
I already took Chauncey on his walk.
我已经带Chauncey散过步了
Well,I heard him coughing.
我听到它在咳嗽
I'm gonna take him to the vet.
我要带他去看兽医
Well,if he's not feeling well,he shouldn't walk.
如果他不舒服 就不该走路
- It's not far. - It is if he can't breathe.
- 不远的 - 如果他不能呼吸了就很远
Don't worry.I'll drive them.
别担心 我会开车带他们去的
I'll get the car.Good day,Mrs.Burke.
我去开车 再见 Burke夫人
Take care,Patrick.
好自为之 Patrick
You too,Liz.
你也是 Liz
- Wait here,and don't move the car. - Yes,sir.
- 在这等着 别把车开走 - 是的 先生
Hey,Peter.Patrick hates the dog.
Peter Patrick讨厌那只狗
Now he's bringing it to the vet.
现在他却带它去看兽医
I heard.You're wired.
我听到了 你装了窃听器
You've gone from My Man Godfrey to Ace Ventura.
你已经从"我的高德弗里" 变成了"宠物侦探"
I'm telling you,he's got another move.
我和你说 他有下一步
- Neal,recon only.You find anything,you pull me in. - You got it.
- Neal 只能侦查 你找到了什么再叫我 - 明白
I feel good.Really good.
我感觉不错 真的不错
Great.You and the Wolcotts' dog.
太好了 你和Wolcotts的狗都是
Patrick went to the vet for himself.
Patrick是为了他自己去兽医那的
I watched the tech remove something from his arm right here.
我看到医生从他手臂里取出了什么
- Plastic? - Yeah.
- 塑料的吗 - 对
- Look like a vein? - I don't know.It was about 2/3 this size.
- 看着像血管吗 - 我不知道 大概这个的2/3
That's a Penrose drain.
那是引流管
There was a case in Florida-- a guy implanted one to fool a DNA test.
在佛罗里达有过这么一个案子 有人植了这个来混过DNA测试
- Filled with someone else's blood? - Yeah.
- 里面装着别人的血吗 - 是
That's why Patrick drew his own.
所以Patrick自己抽的血
This blood was fresh.
血还是新鲜的
Which means 48 hours ago the real Patrick Wolcott was alive.
也就是说48小时前 真的Patrick Wolcott还活着
And in New York.You know,we're kind of good at this.
而且人在纽约 你知道我们很擅长找人
- What? - William's signing over the trust fund tomorrow.
- 什么 - William明天就要在信托基金上签字了
And once fake Patrick gets what he wants...
一旦假Patrick得到了他想要的...
- he won't have any reason to keep the real Patrick around. - No.
- 他不会留下真的Patrick - 不会
We pulled in the vet tech.
我们抓了兽医
Of course he denies implanting a Penrose drain.
当然他不承认帮人植了引流管
We searched the property.No signs of the tubing.
搜了他的地方 也没找到管子的痕迹
We're holding him on suspicion so he can't tip Patrick off?
我们只是怀疑拘留 所以他不能揭发Patrick了吗
You better believe it.
差不多
Well,we won't get a warrant for another DNA testing without permission from the family.
如果家人没有同意 我们就没法再做一次DNA测试
Why don't we just grab the bastard and tell him we know about the drain?
我们为什么不直接抓住那个混蛋 告诉他我们知道血管的事了
Tempting,but we have no leverage.
听着不错 但我们没有筹码
So let's get some leverage.
那就加些筹码
How do we do that?
怎么做
Picasso.
毕加索
Yeah,yeah,Picasso.
对 毕加索
All right,our imposter learned everything he could about Patrick's life.
我们的骗子 尽其所能了解了Patrick的人生
But he didn't know Elizabeth's Picasso story,which proves he doesn't know everything.
但他不知道Elizabeth的毕加索故事 所以说他不是无所不知
Yeah,and he doesn't know what he doesn't know.
他不知道 他不知道什么
We need to ask him something that he thinks only the real Patrick knows the answer to.
我们得问他件让他觉得 真的Patrick会知道答案的事
And give him a reason to get that answer.
让他会去找出答案
Elizabeth asks him about Picasso-- the next morning he knows everything.
Elizabeth问了他毕加索的事 他第二天早上就全知道了
The bike rides.
自行车
He goes on one every morning.It's always for an hour.
他每天早上都骑车出去 一直都是一小时
That's got to be how he's keeping Patrick alive.
那肯定是他保证Patrick活着的办法
- And how he got the Picasso story. - And the blood.
- 以及毕加索的故事 - 还有血
Jones,get a radius set up in op - car,bike,foot,whatever.
Jones 派队人设立监视范围 车 自行车 步行 什么都行
Make sure we stay on him wherever he goes. - Gotcha.
- 确保不管他去哪我们都有人盯着 - 知道了
Patrick was gone for 15 years.
Patrick出走了15年
He probably didn't meet the imposter right away.
他可能不是一开始就遇到了这个骗子
The first time he was spotted after he ran away from boarding school was at Dusseldorf.
他从寄宿学校逃走后 第一次有人看到他是在Dusseldorf
And that's where Leo Kovak comes in.
那是他遇到Leo Kovak的地方
Who is Leo Kovak?
谁是Leo Kovak
He's the reason fake Patrick has to get the answer.
他就是让假Patrick得去找答案的人
I'm Leo Kovak?
我是Leo Kovak吗
You are a very angry Croatian.
你是个非常生气的克罗地亚人
You work for the Von Kesslers,and you want to know what the hell happened in Dusseldorf.
你为Von Kessler家工作 你想知道在Dusseldorf到底发生了什么
What happened in Dusseldorf?
在Dusseldorf发生了什么
It's--it's got to be more convincing.
你得更有说服力
Nothing.But Patrick doesn't know that.
什么都没发生 但Patrick不知道
Croatians invented neckties,
克罗地亚人发明了领带
and I'm sure you've got something in your closet that screams enraged Balkan.
我相信你衣橱里有东西能 代表愤怒的巴尔干半岛
I can't do Croatian.I'm going Polish.
我没法装克罗地亚人人 我要走波兰风
Let's pick out that tie.
那就那样
Mr.Kovak is here to see you.
Kovak先生来见您了
I'm a friend of the Von Kesslers.
我是Von Kessler家的朋友
Of course.The Von Kesslers.
当然 Von Kessler一家
It's been a while since Dusseldorf.
从在Dusseldorf见到你已经很久了
Thank you,Carlyle.
谢谢你 Carlyle
I followed you and your story in the papers,Patrick.
我在报纸上追踪到了你和你的故事 Patrick
That's how we found you.
所以我们找到了你
- I'm sorry.Do I... - You should be sorry for what you did.
- 抱歉 我... - 你是该为你做的感到抱歉
Sir,I don't understand.
先生 我不明白
Don't play stupid.Don't start crying.
别装傻了 别哭
The Von Kesslers pay me to handle their problems.
Von Kessler家付钱让我来解决问题
Is there any way I can pay them for this inconvenience?
能不能用钱来解决这个问题
You think you can put a price on what you did?
你以为你做的事可以估价吗
That money can make this go away?
钱能解决问题吗
No.They want answers.
不 他们想要答案
Compliments of the chef.
主厨推荐
Anything else,sir?
还有别的吗 先生
A pen and something to write.
笔和纸
Call me.We can make Dusseldorf go away.
打给我 我们能让Dusseldorf的事了结
But if you don't,I'll see you at your party tonight.
如果你不解决 今晚宴会见
I'll show myself out.
我自己出去
If I may,sir...
恕我直言 先生...
that threat didn't sound hollow.
那个威胁不像假的
I'm going for a bike ride.
我要出去一下
Enjoy the fresh air.
好好享受新鲜空气
He's exiting the park at Morningside and 116th.
他从Morningside和116街出了公园
I've got him.
我跟上他了
I wouldn't peg you for a fed in this car.
没想到坐着车里的是FBI
Perimeter is all set.
周围都布置好了
We'll pinch Patrick at the location.
我们会找到Patrick的
While we're waiting,may I...
在我们等的时候 我能...
Thanks,Leo.
谢谢你 Leo
North on Manhattan.Handing off.
北曼哈顿 我移交了
Listen to that!
听听!
Hard turn,114th.
急转弯 114街
Agent down!We lost the suspect!
探员被撞倒 嫌疑人跟丢
- Neal,get out. - I'm a butler.
- Neal 出去 - 我是男管家
I'm trained for this.
训练有素
Call an ambulance.All agents to First Avenue and 114th street.
叫救护车来 所有探员到第一大道和114街
Agent Burke and Caffrey are en route.
Burke和Caffrey探员在路上
- Team two has him.West on 116th. - This is 116th.
- 第二队看到他了116街西侧 - 这是116街
Neal.
Neal
- Neal. - Don't look.
- Neal - 别看
I have to look.I can't help it.
我得看 忍不住
There he goes.
他在那
Lost sight of the suspect at the corner of Morningside and 115th.
在Morningside和115街街角 失去嫌疑人踪迹
That must be some butler college.
你肯定上过管家学院
Where's he keeping Patrick?
他把Patrick藏到哪了
He was just here.
他刚刚还在这
Got to be somewhere close.
肯定是附近
All right,we're gonna have to go door to door.
我们得一家家搜了
I want a team on this building,down there,and a team across the street.
我要一队人来这栋楼 然后一队在街对面
Team two,let's go.
第二队 我们走
- Hey,Peter. - Yeah,what do you have?
- Peter - 你发现了什么
This may be a long shot,but Patrick said he dropped his travel journal in the Aegean.
这可能有点玄 但Patrick说过他把旅行日记掉在过爱琴海里
Not exactly the Aegean,but let's have a look.
不一定是爱琴海 我们去看一下吧
For the last time,Dusseldorf.
我再问最后一次 在Dusseldorf
What the hell happened?
到底发生了什么
Nothing happened in Dusseldorf.
在Dusseldorf什么都没发生
The Von Kesslers are pissed,and this Kovaks guy is coming after you.
Von Kessler家很生气 那个叫Kovaks来找你了
I don't know any of these people.
我不认识他们
Okay,fine.Fine.We'll do this the hard way.
好吧 软的不吃我们来硬的
The hard way is what's gonna happen if you don't put that taser down.
如果你不放下电击枪才要吃硬的
Peter Burke,FBI.Cuff him.
Peter Burke FBI 拷上他
- I'm not a butler. - Let's go.
- 我不是管家 - 走吧
Everything's gonna be okay,all right?
一切都会没事的 好吗?
- Patrick. - Dad.
- Patrick - 爸爸
I wanted him to be you so much,I let myself believe.
我太希望他是你了 所以就让自己相信了
I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry I let him into our lives.
对不起 我让他打扰了我们的生活
Liz.
Liz
Bea?
Bea?
You should know,I'm used to being an only child.
你该知道我已经习惯了当独生子
Patrick and Keith- that's his real name-- met on Santorini.
Patrick和Keith 那人的真名 在Santorini认识的
People said they could pass for brothers.
大家都说他们亲如兄弟
When Patrick decided to come home,Keith offered to come with him.
当Patrick决定回家时 Keith说和他一起回来
He took Patrick hostage,read his journals.
他挟持了Patrick 读了他的日记
That man stole his life.
那人偷了他的人生
And now he's got it back again.
现在他拿回来了
- Thanks to you. - Thanks to us.
- 多亏了你们 - 多亏了我们
Are you up for some...some baseball?
你想上垒吗
- A night game? - Yeah.I figured we could pick up where we left off.
- 晚上吗 - 我们可以接着之前的来
I could probably-- Oh,no.
我可能可以 不
Damn it.I'll call Mozzie.
可恶 我得打给Mozzie
Wait,wait,wait,hold on.If you've had this flu already,I think we're safe.
等等 如果你已经得过了 我想我们没事
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-静静的生活
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 安 Zzinc 雅 尘沙 校对: 时差雪 时间轴: 静静的生活
<font color=#238E68>white.collar.Season5Episode5
妙警贼探 第五季 第 5 集